原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译           屯栗子 辰星晓Reginamoon
翻译            DerbyNinja   水龙吟   Kathy567
翻译          海云生 Glida   杏仁斯嘉丽
校对            布塔
时间轴         西·查 Ans 啾 没有影子 紫夏
后期              咖啡·Lee
总监             布塔
听说  要想把故事讲好
They say, if you wanna tell a story right,
就得从头说起
you gotta start at the beginning.
太远了  好吧
Too far? Fine.
这就是我  哈琳·奎泽尔
This is me, Harleen Quinzel.
我小的时候
When I was a kid,
爸爸拿我换了六罐啤酒
my dad traded me for a six-pack of beer.
但不论他抛弃我多少次
But however many times he tried to ditch me...
我都能找回来
I kept coming back.
最后他给我找了个新家
Eventually, he found me a new home.
圣伯纳黛特修道院的好心修女们教会我很多事
The good sisters of St. Bernadette's taught me a lot.
但我从来不是孺子可教的那类孩子
But I was never an establishment kinda gal.
考虑到我经历的一切  我表现得算不错了
All things considered, I did good.
我还去上了大学
I even went to college.
拿了博士学位
Got my PhD.
为爱心碎过一两次
Had my heart broken once or twice.
找寻真爱  可不太容易
Finding love, it's not easy.
所以我全身心投入工作
So I threw myself into my work,
成为一名精神科医生
became a psychiatrist.
就在那时我遇见了他
That's when I met him.
J先生  我的小丑大人
Mr. J. My Joker.
我猛地坠入爱河
Oh, I fell hard.
就像从飞机上跳下来  没带降落伞
Like out of a plane without a parachute,
正中你那张蠢兮兮的脸一样惨
right in your dumb fucking face kinda hard.
我完全迷失了自我
I lost all sense of who I was.
只看得到我亲爱的布丁
I only had eyes for Puddin'.
我们都知道那句话怎么说
We all know the saying,
"每个成功男人背后
"Behind every successful man
都有一个坏婆娘"
there's a badass broad."
好吧  说的就是我
Well, that was me.
J先生最伟大的花招中  有一些是我想到的
I was the brains behind some of Mr. J's greatest stunts.
但他只是没告诉别人罢了
Not that he let anyone know it.
布丁
Puddin'?
可能所有的好事总会结束吧
I guess all good things have to come to an end.
于是
So...
我们分手了
we broke up.
我非常成熟地接受了此事
I handled it real mature.
但J先生受到了极大的冲击
But Mr. J was super broke up about it.
我换了一个很不错的地方  一个人住
I got an amazing new place that was all mine.
让我有空间去反思自己过去犯下的错误
It gave me the space to really reflect on the mistakes of my past.
我需要找到自己的新身份
I had to find a new identity.
新的我
A new me.
很不容易
It wasn't easy.
但过了一段时间  我甚至开始
But after a while, I even opened myself up
拥抱可能的新恋情
to the possibility of new love.
嗨  小可人儿
Hello, nice baby.
新恋情是这样的
Here's the thing about new love...
我接受肉体支付
I take payment-in-kind.
你得喂它才行
...you have to feed it.
不久后我就完全恢复
Soon enough, I was back on my feet.
准备好翻篇  去交新朋友
Ready to move on, to make new friends.
她是货真价实的
She means fucking business!
-来了  -给我借点力
- Oh, here we go! - Whip me!
她借力冲到了最前面
She has taken a whip from the pivot, catapulted to the high side!
来吧
Yeah! Come on!
是时候让哥谭市见识一下新的哈莉·奎茵了
It was time for Gotham to meet the new Harley Quinn,
所以我真的是豁出去了
so I really put myself out there.
像骑你男人一样骑那根杆子吧
Ride that pole like you ride your man!
该死  给我他妈坐下
God damn it. Sit the fuck down.
什么
What?
我说了把你的小屁股放下去  你这个蠢婊子
I said sit your skinny ass down, you dumb slut.
好吧
Okay.
你把我的腿坐断了
You broke my fucking legs!
怎么了
What?
无名场面不派对  对吧
It's not a party without a little drama, am I right?
来呀  开灯
Come on! Turn it up!
我请大家喝酒
Shots on the house.
敢说我傻  我有博士学位  混账东西
Call me dumb. I have a PhD, motherfucker.
-奎茵小姐  -罗米
- Miss Quinn. - Romy.
他是我的司机
That was my driver.
哎呀
Oh, whoops.
这肯定是他的错  我炒了他
Well, I'm sure it was his fault. Consider him fired.
我很感激
Consider me grateful.
尤其是我知道你不喜欢我
Especially since I know you don't like me.
我刺激了他那微妙的心理平衡
I agitate his already delicate sense of mental equilibrium.
和他那必须要成为注意力中心的
That and his obsessive-compulsive need
强迫性的内心需求
to be the center of attention.
你的情人今晚会来吗
Will your paramour be joining us this evening?
今晚不会  罗米  今晚不会
Not tonight, Romy. Not tonight.
好好享受  奎茵小姐
Well, enjoy yourself, Miss Quinn.
请代我向小丑问好
And do give the Joker my best.
好吧  我还没告诉别人我俩分手了
Okay, fine, so I hadn't told people about the breakup.
但你们不会懂的
But you don't understand.
给我找个新司机
Find me a new driver.
做小丑的女友给了我豁免权
Being Joker's girl gave me immunity.
我可以做我想做的事  当我想当的人
I could do whatever I wanted to whoever I wanted,
没有人敢反对
and no one ever dared to object.
别让他给你脸色  好吗
And don't let him give you shit, okay?
你得为你自己撑腰
You have to stick up for yourself.
算了吧  没过几天他们就会复合了
Oh, please. I give it a few days before they're back together.
就算我真的告诉大家了
Even when I did try and tell people,
他们也不相信我
they didn't believe me.
拜托  她跟我说他们这次真的分手了
Come on. She told me they're really broken up this time.
当然了  谢尔
Sure they are, Shell.
所以她还戴着那条俗气的J字项链
That's why she's still wearing that tacky "J" necklace.
只要小丑打个响指  她就会立即
She is going to be running right back into his arms
扑向他的怀抱
the minute he snaps his fingers.
就算不是他  随便哪个活着的大男子主义者都行
If not him, the next closest alpha male with a pulse.
有些人天生就是扶不起的阿斗
Some people just aren't born to stand on their own.
-姑娘们  喝一杯  来吧  -好
- Oh, girl, let's drink. Come on. - All right.
我知道自己需要找个办法告诉全世界
I knew I needed to find some way to show the world
我要永远地跟J先生划清界限
that I'd cut ties with Mr. J for good.
哈莉
Harley!
有些人的回忆是埃菲尔铁塔  或橄榄花园
Some people have the Eiffel Tower, or Olive Garden.
小丑和我呢
The Joker and I?
我们的爱之花盛开在剧毒物质加工厂里
Our love bloomed in a highly toxic industrial processing plant.
很幸运的是
And luckily for me,
我的好主意都是喝醉后想出来的
I have all my best ideas drunk.
我想到一个超棒的主意
I have the best idea!
什么鬼  快回来
The fuck? Hey! Hey! Come back here!
这里是一切开始的地方  布丁
This is where it all began, Puddin'.
你这个混蛋
You motherfucker!
正是我需要的体面的结束
It was the closure I needed.
新的开始
A fresh start.
做自己的机会
A chance to be my own woman.
但我可不是哥谭市唯一需要自我解放的女人
But I wasn't the only dame in Gotham looking for emancipation.
这是我们的故事
This is our story.
因为是我讲  所以老子想从哪里开始就从哪里开始
And I'm telling it, so I'll start where I fucking want.
见见警方吧
Meet the cop.
五十块打赌是地盘争夺战
I got 50 says it was turf war.
不是他
Not him.
一如既往  你赌错了  芒罗
Well, as always, you're wrong, Munroe.
这位  芮妮·蒙托亚
Her. Renee Montoya.
从小看八十年代警匪剧
Raised on '80s cop shows,
她总会说些俗气的名台词  比如
she's always saying cheesy shit like...
只有一个枪手
There was only one shooter.
在屋里
Inside.
这个人开枪把玻璃打碎了
This guy shot out the glass.
塞拉诺
Serrano.
让弹道专家在这些停放的车里检查是否有子弹
Have Ballistics check for a bullet in one of those parked cars.
十年前  她破了一个能平步青云的案子
Ten years ago, she broke a career-making case.
-我结巴了吗  -快去
- Did I stutter? - Go ahead.
但当时她的搭档却把功劳都抢去了
But her partner at the time took all the credit.
所以他荣升了警长
So while he made captain,
她却只能当警探  跟这个蠢货搭档
she got stuck at detective level with this idiot.
好吧  你觉得是一个人打死四个吗
Okay, you think one guy got all four?
等等  等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait.
我只是说我们发现了四具尸体
I'm just saying, we got four dead bodies here, you know.
-一个人...弹孔  -我在努力查案
- One guy... Bullet holes. - I'm trying to work.
抱歉  你工作吧  忙吧
I'm sorry. Go ahead and work. Go ahead.
枪手走到跟前时还没拔枪  六发子弹
The shooter got close before drawing. Six rounds.
这里三个人每人两发
Two for each of these three.
当心你自己吧
Yo, mind your debt.
-我跟你说  -那个叫安吉拉的女孩  她是个公主
- I'm telling you. - That girl, Angelina, she's a princess.
你看看
Look at this.
-是万圣节打扮吗  -你好吗
- Is it Halloween? - Hey. How you doing?
与其他人无关
And it wasn't about them.
枪手是冲这个人来的
It was all about this guy, right here.
你知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
他妈的贱人
You fucking bitch.
穿过他喉咙的这支箭
And this arrow through his throat...
她想让他慢慢死去
She wanted him to die slowly.
-她  -我们找到了头发
- She? - We got a hair.
他找到了新杀手
And he's got a new assassin.
谁
Who does?
罗曼·博伟·赛恩尼斯
Roman Beauvais Sionis.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
我是蒙托亚  刚刚怎么回事
This is Montoya. What the hell was that?
该死
Shit.
-警探  -怎么
- Detective. - Yep?
我们找到这条项链
Found this necklace.
我操
Holy shit.
干得漂亮  警官
Good work, Officer.
怎么了
What is it?
哈莉·奎茵和小丑分手了
Harley Quinn and the Joker broke up.
什么
What?
这是他们的秘密地点
This was their spot.
她刚刚公开更新了自己的恋爱状态
She just publicly updated her relationship status.
哈莉·奎茵刚刚把自己解禁了
Harley Quinn just called open season on herself.
她可没想明白
She did not think this one through.
对  我的确没想明白
Yeah, no shit I didn't think it through.
我即将了解到  在这个城市里
I'm about to learn that a lot of people
有很多人想要我的命
in this city want me dead.
在名单上的第一位就是这个人
And at the top of that list is this guy.
乔先生和他可爱的妻女
Mr. Keo and his lovely wife and daughter.
是你逼我的
You kinda forced my hand here.
说实话  我有点失望
Gotta say, I'm a little disappointed.
我给了你一份好活计  对吧
I gave you a great pitch. Didn't I?
而我以为...
And I thought...
我以为我们能一起造出点美好的记忆
I thought we could build something beautiful together.
我以为我们可以成为家人
I thought we could be family.
我来放你自由
I'm gonna set you free.
她怎么办
What about her?
我想我们可以放她走
I think we can let her go.
这场大戏传递出的信息足够响亮了
I mean, this is a pretty loud fucking shitshow of a message.
宝贝
Baby.
别哭
Don't cry.
谢谢  谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
那是鼻涕泡吗
Is that a snot bubble?
-恶心  -什么
- Gross. - What?
我改主意了  剥了她
Oh, I've changed my mind. Peel it off.
不  不
No. No!
这位嗜好剥人脸皮的疯子
The wack job with the penchant for peeling faces
叫罗曼·赛恩尼斯
is Roman Sionis,
代号
aka
黑面具
Black Mask.
我尚且不知道他想要我死这件事
The fact that he wants me dead hasn't yet hit my radar.
你瞧  我当时身处半个城市之外
See, I was halfway across town,
宿醉  想着早餐的事儿
hungover, and thinking about breakfast.
鸡蛋  培根  美国芝士
Egg, bacon, American cheese.
松软的  烤过的  抹黄油的面包
Soft, toasted buttered roll.
加上少许辣酱
Just a dash of hot sauce.
别太多  萨尔
Not too much, Sal.
我要尝到芝士味
I wanna taste the cheese.
真是开启新生活的绝妙方式呀
What a way to start my new life.
用一个完美的鸡蛋三明治
With the perfect egg sandwich.
你真是我的救星  萨尔
You're a lifesaver, Sal.
欠你的75美分我会还的  行吗
And I'm good for the 75 cents, okay?
我发誓  我就只剩这么点家底了
I promise. That's all the money I got in the world,
花在这上面简直超值
and it's so worth it.
我不知道是因为他亚美尼亚手臂上稀疏的毛发
I don't know if it's the stray Armenian arm hair,
还是因为他的芝士片总是过期六个月
or the fact that his cheese slices are always six months out of date,
但萨尔做的鸡蛋三明治无人能比
but no one makes an egg sandwich like Sal.
我认真的  萨尔  无人能比
I mean it, Sal. No one.
不许动  哥谭警局
Freeze! Gotham PD.
我才不呢
Yeah, I don't think so.
你他妈是在逗我吗
Are you fucking kidding me?
警察
Police.
距离我用顶尖化工那个小花招
It had been six short hours
向世界宣告我和J先生已经是过去式了
since my little stunt at Ace Chemicals
才过去了短短六小时
announced to the world that Mr. J and I were dunzo.
我长久以来享受的豁免就已经失效了
The immunity I'd enjoyed for so long was gone.
以前从来不敢找我麻烦的条子
Cops who never would've dared come after me before
忽然就这样对我了
were suddenly doing this.
站住
Freeze!
-你知道更糟的是什么吗  -闪开
- And what's worse? - Move!
以前我得罪过的每一个人
Every person I ever wronged
现在都觉得可以来找我报仇了
now felt free to come and take their pound of flesh.
万万没想到我得罪了好多人
Turns out I wronged a lot of people.
来吧  乖乖  咬他
Come on, boy. Get him!
终于
Finally.
然后...
And then...
我们会共渡难关的  好吗
We're gonna get through this, okay?
悲剧降临了
...tragedy struck.
唯有失去了我真正热爱的东西
It took losing something I truly love
我才意识到  我背上的靶子
for me to see that the target on my back
比我想象中要大
was bigger than I thought.
不许动
Freeze.
随着包围圈渐渐向我收紧
With the walls closing in around me,
我采取了一个精心计算过的
I made a carefully calculated,
极具战略性的举动
highly strategic move.
好吧
Fine.
是瞎猫碰着死耗子了  但还是...
It was dumb luck. But still...
那感觉挺棒的
That felt pretty great.
抱歉忽然闯进你家
Sorry for busting in on you like that,
谢谢让我抄近路啦
but thanks for the shortcut.
再见
See ya.
她在这呢
There she is.
哈莉·奎茵
Harley Quinn.
怎么了
Yeah?
我等这一刻等了好久了
I've waited a long time for this.
这样啊
You have?
我还没吃早餐呢
I haven't had breakfast yet.
我怎么你了
What did I do to you?
你在逗我吗
Are you serious?
看看我的脸
Look at my face.
看  看  我  的  脸
Look at my face!
那又不是我干的
That wasn't me.
但是你怂恿他干的
But you dared him to do it.
是啦  但我怂恿了很多人做了很多事呀
Yeah, but I dare a lot of people to do a lot of things, okay?
拜托  我俩现在甚至都不在一起了
Come on. I'm not even with him anymore.
我知道
I know.
那意味着
That means
没有人来阻止我了
there's no one here to stop me.
-好吧  -你死定了  奎茵
- Right. - You're gonna die, Quinn.
一分钱
A penny.
怎么还开始射箭了
They're shooting arrows now?
该死
Ah, crap.
他也来
Him, too?
和谈
Parley?
我操  蒙托亚  你闻着像是死老鼠的屁眼
Fuck, Montoya, you smell like a dead rat's asshole.
今天别惹我  辛普森
Not today, Simpson.
这可是蒙托亚警探  对前辈放尊敬点
It's Detective Montoya. Respect your elders.
我是说  对老人家
I mean, your elderly.
你只比我年轻几岁
You're only a few years younger than me,
却还在做前台工作
and you're still behind that desk.
还要继续说下去吗
You wanna go there?
快点  把口袋里的东西都掏出来  全部
Come on. Empty your pockets. All of it.
卡珊德拉·该隐  这就又进来了
Cassandra Cain, back already?
还以为事到如今你已经学会不被抓的办法了呢
Thought by now you'd figure out how not to get caught.
怎么  居然不回嘴
What? No comeback?
你还好吧
You all right?
你闻着像屎
You smell like shit.
辛普森
Yo, Simpson.
失物招领处有干净衣服吗
Any clean clothes in lost and found?
这些可是很严重的指控  蒙托亚小姐
These are serious accusations, Miss Montoya.
赛恩尼斯这个姓氏
The Sionis family name
在哥谭市一半的博物馆和学校前挂着呢
is on half the museums and schools in Gotham.
这就能让他免受法律制裁了吗  警长
And that makes him immune to the law, Captain?
蒙托亚那天的遭遇几乎和我一样悲惨了
Montoya's day is going almost as badly as mine.
还记得那个抢了她的升职的人吗
Remember the guy who stole her promotion?
就是他
That's him.
光昨晚一晚上他就让人杀了四个人
He had four people killed alone last night.
如果罗曼·赛恩尼斯真这么神机妙算
If Roman Sionis is such a mastermind,
他怎么还被自家公司炒了
how'd he get fired from his own fucking company?
杰纳斯集团是他爸的公司  谢谢
The Janus Corporation is his father's company, thank you.
顺便一提  他被逐出继承人行列了
And by the way, they cut him off.
地检办公室对这件事是什么立场
Where does the DA's office stand on all this?
更糟糕的是  这位助理地检
To make matters worse, the assistant DA?
是她的前女友
That's her ex.
证明赛恩尼斯和这些谋杀案有关的证据...
The evidence that Sionis is linked to these murders...
有一批货要来了
There's a shipment coming in.
毒品吗
Drugs?
-一颗钻石  -一颗钻石
- A diamond. - A diamond.
你可真行  蒙托亚
Wow, Montoya.
我们要不要打电话给联调局求助
Should we call the Feds for backup?
听着  我在那家夜店有个线人
Listen, I had a source at the club.
他的司机
His driver.
他说罗曼一直在叨叨这件事
He said that Roman couldn't stop talking about this thing.
他还说自己听到了关于激光加密之类的东西
And he said that he overheard something about laser-encoding.
我做了些调查
Now, I did some research.
我觉得是贝尔蒂内利钻石
I think it's the Bertinelli diamond.
你还记得贝尔蒂内利灭门案吧
You remember the Bertinelli massacre, right?
历史小课堂
Quick history lesson.
十五年前
Fifteen years ago,
哥谭市最有钱的黑手党家族之一被灭门了
one of the wealthiest mafia families in Gotham was gunned down.
是为了夺权  但真正的目标
It was a power grab, but the real target
是贝尔蒂内利家绝密的离岸账户
was the Bertinellis' super-secret offshore bank accounts,
据说其相关信息被加密在了
the details of which were said to be encoded
一颗三十克拉的钻石的原子结构上
in the atomic structure of a 30-carat diamond.
这颗钻石失踪了
The rock was lost.
找到它
And with it,
就找到了通向贝尔蒂内利财富的唯一钥匙
the only key to the Bertinelli fortune.
正因如此罗曼·赛恩尼斯才想抢到它
Which is exactly why Roman Sionis is trying to get his hands on it.
所以他是个非常危险的人物
That's what makes him so dangerous.
他已经在建造一支军队了
He's already building an army.
如果他得到了那颗钻石
If he gets the diamond,
他就有金钱有门路
he'll have all the money and connections
去贿赂他需要的每一个法官  每一个警察
to bribe every single judge and cop he needs
以垄断这座城市
to get a monopoly on the city.
你刚说你在内部有线人吗
You said you had someone on the inside?
没错  他...
Yes. He's...
他现在已经不在那里了  但...
He's no longer there, but...
所以说起来  你手上什么都没有
So basically, you have nothing.
你试图对付
You are trying to go after
哥谭市最不怕打官司也最有钱的家族之一
one of the most litigious and wealthiest families in Gotham,
而你却只能依赖传闻和直觉
and all you've got is rumors and a hunch?
地检办公室也在试图立案起诉他
Well, you know, the DA's office is building a case against him, too.
对吧  易小姐
Isn't that right, Miss Yee?
听着  如果地检大人想在这件事上出头
Listen, if the DA is willing to throw himself out in front of this,
-我无所谓  -警长  不是
- it's fine with me. - Captain, no.
听着  芒罗
Listen, Munroe,
给我找些能指控赛恩尼斯的切实证据  好吗
find me some tangible connection to Sionis, all right?
-遵命  长官  -等等  等等  警长
- Yes, sir. - Wait, wait, wait. Captain.
这是我的案子
This is my case, okay?
我已经查了六个月了
I've been working on this for six months.
我们需要一些真正能用得上的东西  警探
We need something that we can actually use, Detective.
还有  蒙托亚小姐  我们是有着装要求的
And, Miss Montoya, we do have a dress code.
-我很抱歉  但我...  -不
- Look, I'm sorry about that, but I... - No.
你这是在拿我的工作乱搞
That is my job you are fucking with.
你什么毛病  芮妮
What is wrong with you, Renee?
我  他把我的案子给别人了
Me? He gave my case away.
可怜的芮妮
Oh, poor Renee.
不如给你自己倒杯酒喝吧  快到中午了
Why don't you pour yourself a drink? It's almost noon.
老天  谁他妈给我打电话
Jesus. Who the fuck is this?
-什么事  -你他妈为什么不接电话
- What? - Why the fuck haven't you been picking up your phone?
出事了
We've got a situation.
出...出什么事了
What... What situation?
这件事不是我告诉你的
You didn't hear this from me,
但你得抢在别人之前找到她
but you gotta find her before someone else does.
钻石在她手上
She's got the diamond,
相信我  罗曼会杀了她的
and trust me, Roman will kill her.
我的钻石  谁  在谁手上
My diamond? Who? Who's got it?
一个孩子
This kid.
是个扒手  叫卡珊德拉·该隐
She's a pickpocket. Her name's Cassandra Cain.
见鬼了
Holy fuck.
有什么需要帮忙吗
Can I help you?
有的  你能帮到我的
Why, yes. Yes, you can.
我是来报告一起可怕的犯罪的
I'm here to report a terrible crime.
是什么可怕的犯罪
And what terrible crime is that?
这个
This one.
好呀  小伙子们
Hi, boys.
散会咯
Meeting's over.
跑啊  小猪快跑
Run, piggy, run.
卡珊德拉·该隐在哪
Where can I find Cassandra Cain?
等等  等等  我讲得不对
Hold up, hold up. I'm telling this all wrong.
倒带一下
Let's rewind.
要让你们理解
For you to understand why me,
为什么我  警察和马桶上那位女士
the cop, and that dame on the toilet...
她叫卡珊德拉·该隐
Her name's Cassandra Cain.
都在找这位叫该隐的
...are all looking for this Cain character...
我得带你回到几天之前
I gotta take you back a few days,
带你回到我在黑面具夜店喝到烂醉的那晚
to that night I got shitfaced at the Black Mask Club.
? 这是男人的世界 ?
? This is a man's world ?
这位是黛娜·兰斯
This is Dinah Lance.
? 但它什么也不是 ?
? But it would be nothing ?
但她更喜欢别人叫她黑金丝雀
But she prefers Black Canary.
? 什么也不是 ?
? Nothing ?
她有迷死人的嗓音
She's got a killer voice.
但那晚出了其他的岔子
But there was some other shit going down that night.
...像这样临时通知
...short notice like this.
我说的不是貌合神离的搭档
I'm not talking superficial partnerships.
我说的是你我互相照应
I'm talking you and me having each other's backs.
金狮帮不能大摇大摆地走进哥谭国家银行
The Golden Lions can't just wander into Gotham National Bank.
我能
I can.
贷款  流动资金  洗钱
Loans, liquidity, laundering.
要是你带你的人参与进来
Look, if you bring your boys into the fold,
我们一起  要什么有什么
there are no limits to what we could achieve together.
我在构建特别的计划
I'm building something special.
感谢你的邀请  赛恩尼斯先生
I appreciate your offer, Mr. Sionis.
但恕我直言
But with all due respect,
金狮帮是我们的家族事业
the Golden Lions are a family business.
去他的家庭  无意冒犯  但去他的
Fuck family. All due respect, but fuck that.
家庭就是幻觉
Family's a fucking illusion.
你知道我家给了我什么吗  什么都没有
You know what my family gave me? Nothing.
我知道传言怎么说
I know what everyone says.
"罗曼·赛恩尼斯
"Here comes Roman Sionis.
他是含着银汤匙出生的"
He was handed life on a silver spoon."
"凌晨五点喝金汤力"  "我想吃鸭子"
"Gin and tonics at 5:00." "I'll have the duck."
诸如此类的  捏造的胡话
Blah, blah, blah. Fake fucking fucks.
但你看我现在
But look at me now.
我找到了贝尔蒂内利钻石
I've located the Bertinelli diamond.
马上这座城市就是我的了
I'm about to own this city.
不仅是东区
Not just the East End.
我想得很宏伟  宝贝
I am thinking big, baby.
我想让你跟我一起
And I want you there with me.
建立我们自己的家庭
We could make our own family.
赛恩尼斯先生
Mr. Sionis,
金狮帮在哥谭市运作已经将近一百年了
the Golden Lions have operated in Gotham for nearly 100 years.
我们不需要你的保护
We have no need of your protection.
他会后悔的
He's gonna regret that.
你能不能好好考虑一下  就当是为了我
Will you sleep on it? Will you do that for me?
跟你那美娇妻说一说
Run it by that beautiful wife of yours,
后天我们码头见
and I'll come see you at the docks, day after tomorrow.
好吗
Okay?
? 这是男人的世界 ?
? This is a man's world ?
? 但它什么也不是 ?
? It would be nothing ?
? 如果没有女性的话 ?
? Without a woman or a girl ?
谁玩得很开心  你们玩得很开心
Who's having a good time? You are.
餐食还不错吧
Food is good?
还需要鸡尾酒吗
Do you need any more cocktails?
干杯  祝你们健康
Your good health.
? 他迷失在寂寞中 ?
? He's lost in the loneliness ?
? 他迷失了 ?
? He's lost ?
? 这是男人的世界 ?
? This is a man's world ?
? 但它什么也不是 ?
? It wouldn't be nothing ?
? 如果没有女性的话 ?
? Without a woman or a girl ?
金丝雀在罗曼的酒吧唱了好多年
Canary's been singing at Roman's club for years.
掌声
Come on!
他叫她"我的小鸟"
He calls her his little bird,
她被他牢牢攥在手心里
and he's got her wrapped right around his fancy little finger.
给  金丝雀
Here you go, Canary.
谢谢
Thank you.
"雇佣兵"怎么写
How do you spell "mercenary"?
雇佣乒...
Merceninny...
雇佣乓
Merceran?
歌手女士
Singer lady woman!
你真的很棒
You're really, really good.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道什么是丑角吗
Know what a harlequin is?
化着乱七八糟眼妆的蹩脚小丑
Janky-ass clown with bad eye makeup?
丑角的任务
A harlequin's role
是服务
is to serve.
服务观众
An audience.
服务主人
A master.
丑角没有正主就什么都不是
You know, a harlequin's nothing without a master.
没人在乎我们其他的身份
And no one gives two fucks who we are beyond that.
我不知道你觉得我是谁  女士
Yeah, I don't know who you think I am, lady,
但你说的不是我
but I'm not her.
布丁和我分手了
Puddin' and I broke up.
我谁也没告诉
I haven't told that to anyone.
是啊
Yeah.
这次断得一干二净了
For good this time.
这是我好久以来第一次
And for the first time in a long time,
独自一个人
I'm all on my lonesome.
太好了
It's great.
欢迎加入独身俱乐部
Welcome to the club.
谢谢
Thanks.
别一个人  再喝一杯怎么样
Hey, don't be lonesome. How about another drink?
-太好了  -好吗
- Yes! - Yeah?
-好  -我请你
- Yeah. - It's on me.
-好  上酒  -双份
- Sure. Drinks! - Hey, two shots.
我们没事
We're all good here.
-我不想回家  -不想回吗
- I don't wanna go home. - Oh, no? No.
不
No.
你想吐就告诉我
Let me know if you're gonna get sick.
你的座驾来了  来吧
Your chariot's arrived. Oh, there you go.
我们不吃早餐吗
Are we getting breakfast?
哥们  帮我一把
Hey, buddy, I'm gonna need some help.
这是我朋友
This is my friend.
我跟你说过...
I told you all about...
去开车门  我扶着她  我扶着她
Hey, get the door, man. I got her, I got her.
-好了  -等等
- There we go. - Wait.
这不是小丑的女人吗
Isn't that Joker's girl?
不再是了
Not anymore.
还能再坐一个人吗
Got room for one more?
我不需要你帮忙  我搞得定
I don't need your help. I got this.
你搞得定  你确定
You got this? You sure about that?
是啊  怪不得大家都恨你
Yeah, no wonder everyone hates you.
你搞得定
You got this!
你们混蛋
You motherfucker!
瞧瞧  瞧瞧
Well, well, well, well, well, well.
那是我们的兰斯小姐吗
Could that be our little Miss Lance?
这么多年  我还以为
All these years, I thought she was just
她只有漂亮脸蛋和一对铁肺
a pretty face and a fine set of lungs.
扎斯先生  我有个绝妙的主意
Mr. Zsasz, I've had an amazing idea.
那才是我的小鸟
That's my little bird.
别碰你买不起的东西  先生
Don't touch what you can't afford, mister.
闭嘴
Shut up.
歌女
Oh, songbird.
你的驾驶技术和你的身手一样好吗
You drive as good as you fight?
谁问的
Who's asking?
老大
The boss.
你升职了
You're getting promoted.
你是他的司机了
You're his new driver.
谢了  但我唱唱歌就行了
Huh. Thanks, but I think I'm good with the singing gig.
你开车也会开得很好的
You'll be good at the driving gig.
明天早上九点整到这里
Be here tomorrow. 9:00 a.m. Sharp.
所以金丝雀就这样获得了
So, that's how Canary got herself a job
为哥谭市新任教父开车的工作
driving around Gotham's newest Godfather.
我要补充  如若不是在下帮忙
A position, I might add, that wouldn't have been vacant
这个职位可是不会招人的
without the help of yours truly.
早
Morning.
是你想要孩子
You're the one who wanted the kid!
我从没想要过她
I never wanted her!
让我猜猜  父母吗
Let me guess. Parents?
养父母
Foster parents.
对
Right.
抱歉  小鬼
Sorry, kid.
抱歉你个头
Sorry about your face.
该死  你头上真的受伤了
Shit, you do have something on your face.
另一个人更惨
You should've seen the other guy.
我要那个该死的崽子滚出我家
I want that kid out of my fucking house!
小鬼  不是每天都会这样
You know, kid, not every day is gonna be like this.
你得坚持住
You just gotta hang in there.
找点东西吃
Get something to eat.
别掺和  不值得
Stay outta that. It's not worth it.
别那么跟我说话
Don't talk to me like that.
第二周  金丝雀都在
Canary spends the next week
熟悉给罗曼当私人司机的工作
settling in to her new job as Roman's personal driver.
真恶心  走吧
Ew. Okay.
她不知道的是
What she didn't know
给剥脸皮先生开车
is that driving Mr. Face-peely-pants
会让她正巧位于
was gonna put her right in the crosshairs
我最爱的警察的瞄准镜中心
of my favorite little piggy.
黛娜·兰斯
Dinah Lance?
你是谁
Who the hell are you?
我是芮妮·蒙托亚  哥谭警局的警探
I'm Renee Montoya, detective with GCPD.
前一任司机和我达成了协议
Your predecessor and I had an arrangement.
是吗
Oh, really?
他告诉我有货要到了  一颗钻石
He told me that there was a shipment coming in. A diamond.
一颗非常特别的钻石
A very special diamond.
我不感兴趣  女士  谢谢你的咖啡
Yeah, not interested, lady. Thanks for the coffee.
你知道你在为谁工作吗
Do you know who you're working for?
你说得对  我知道
You're damn right, I do.
就是他给了我一份工作  让我不用流浪街头
He's the man who gave me a job. Took me off the streets.
对  他也是个非常危险的人物
Yeah, well, he's also a very dangerous man.
一个罪犯  一个凶手
A criminal. A murderer.
你妈妈天上有灵
What would your mother think of you
要是知道你为这种人工作会怎么想
working for a guy like that, huh?
你跟她有相同的能力
You have the same power she had.
她是不是也想让你好好利用呢
Don't you think she would want you to use it?
你对我妈妈一无所知
The hell do you know about my mother?
以前  她曾经协助过哥谭警局
Back in the day, she used to help the GCPD.
-她是个好人  -是啊
- She was a good woman. - Yeah.
她是个非常好的女人
She was a damn good woman.
那种舍己为人的好女人
The kind of woman who put everyone else's lives before her own.
当她被发现死在路边时
And when she was found dead in the street,
你人在哪  你们警察又在哪
where the fuck were you and your boys in blue then?
现在你跑上门来
Now you wanna come and knock on my door
叫我帮你
and ask me to help you out
犯下和她当年一样的错吗
and make the same mistake she did?
那祝你好运
Yeah. Good luck with that.
你说得也对
That's fair enough.
很遗憾你失去了她
And I'm sorry for your loss.
我得声明
For the record,
在我的管辖之下绝对不会再发生这种事
that would never happen on my watch.
斯普兰桥战士投响了
The Sprang Bridge Soldiers capituated.
是投降  他们当然投降了
"Capitulated." Of course they did.
我和你说过干掉乔能杀鸡儆猴
I told you that Keo scene would send a message.
是的  老大
It sure did, boss.
太管用了
It sure fucking did.
十字弓杀手
Crossbow Killer
昨晚又出手了
struck again last night.
杀了罗西和他的四个手下
Rossi and four of his guys.
没有我的允许  谁都不许杀我的小弟
People don't kill people I own without my permission.
为什么这个十字弓男不知道规矩
Why doesn't this crossbow guy know that?
-你知道  -我知道
- You know that! - I know it.
为什么这个十字弓男不知道
Why doesn't this crossbow guy?
十字弓男为什么不是我的小弟
Why don't I own the crossbow guy?
-他应该认你做老大  -我喜欢十字弓
- You should own him. - I mean, I like crossbows.
早上好  早上好
Good morning. Good morning.
-早  -请进  请进
- Morning. - Come in. Come in.
我们刚谈了点小事  到处转转
We're just finishing up a little business. Look around.
-你迟到了  -没关系
- You're late. - It's fine.
她应该改天再来  因为她迟到了
Should she come back another time, 'cause she's late?
不  很漂亮吧
No. Isn't this stunning?
那是乔奎人面具
That is a Chokwe mask.
我去刚果金沙萨
I got it when I was embedded
姆冈尼部落时得到的
with the Mbangani tribe in Congo-Kinshasa.
-你去过吗  -没去过
- Have you ever been? - I've never been.
-听说那里很美  -脏死了
- I've heard it's beautiful. - It's dirty.
来看看这个
Here, look at this.
货真价实的参沙  也就是干缩人头
Genuine tsantsa or shrunken head.
厄瓜多尔的舒阿尔族
Shuar of Ecuador.
他们都是厉害人物  出奇的温柔
They're amazing people. Surprisingly gentle.
-你应该会喜欢他们的  -真的吗
- I think you might like them. - Really?
他们把敌人的头煮熟
They boil the heads of their enemies
做成这些小脑袋
and they make these little fellas.
很精致吧  看看
Exquisite, aren't they? Look.
看看这些小耳朵  可爱的发型
Look at those little ears. And his little haircut.
他已经一千岁了
Yeah, he's 1,000 years old.
-厉害  -但现在只是我客厅的装饰品
- Wow. - And now he's just an ornament in my living room.
-恶心  我喜欢  -是吗
- Ew! I love it. - Yeah?
这是古代针灸模型
These are ancient acupuncture models.
你看到了  他们身上都有针灸穴位
As you can see, they have all the acupuncture points.
我们在山里挖出来的
And we found these buried in the mountains.
昨晚顶尖化工被炸飞了
Ace Chemicals got blown sky high last night.
行  行  我们去找那个十字弓杀手  我知道了
All right, all right, let's find the Crossbow Killer. I get it.
-继续...  -他也是针灸模型吗
- So... - Is he an acupuncture model, too?
他不是针灸模型
He is not an acupuncture model.
这是我的雕像
This is a statue of me.
是由哥谭市知名艺术家雕刻的
It was made by a very famous Gotham artist...
哈莉·奎茵炸的
Harley Quinn did it.
向小丑示威  叫他去死之类的
Some kind of "fuck you" to the Joker.
他们分手了
They split.
你怎么回事  维克多
What's wrong with you, Victor?
-这么重要的事怎么不先说  -就是
- Talk about burying the lede. - Yeah.
这可是天大的好消息
This is spectacular news!
她不属于他  她是属于我的
She doesn't belong to him, she belongs to me.
派人去找她
Have the boys go find her.
围堵她  把她带回来  我要她
Round her up, bring her back. I want her.
你  我有东西要你去帮我拿
You, I have something I want you to pick me up.
非常重要的东西
Something super-duper important, okay?
-好  -我跟你一起去
- Okay. - I'll go with you.
-跟维克多一起去  -只是去拿东西而已
- Yeah, go with Victor. - It's just a pickup. I mean...
不  他不会伤害你
No, he's harmless.
照做  快去
Do as you're told. Go.
好  我们可以走了
All right. We can go.
给我拿
I'll take that.
赛先生说让我拿着
Mr. S said for me to hold on to it.
去把车开过来
Go get your car.
这颗钻石就要变成
That rock. That rock's about to become the key
我能否活着享受新独立的关键
to whether or not I live to enjoy my newfound independence.
放开我
Get off me.
你在这里干什么
What the hell are you doing here?
不是只有你一个人
You're not the only one who makes money
从那些人傻钱多的白人身上赚钱
off of dumb, rich, white people.
知道吗
Well, you know what?
总有一天你会惹到不该招惹的人的  妹子
One day you're gonna pick the wrong pocket, sis.
随便吧
Okay. Whatever.
蠢小鬼
Dumb-ass kids.
借过  抱歉
Excuse me. Sorry.
我真的很喜欢你的耳环
I really like your earrings.
谢谢你
Why, thank you.
就是她  小偷就是她
There's the thief. There's the thief.
放开我
Get off of me!
那小女孩偷了我的手表
That little girl took my watch.
我什么也没做
I didn't do nothing.
钻石去哪了
Where the fuck's the diamond?
我刚刚还拿着
I just fucking had it.
卡珊
Cass!
等等
Wait!
等一下
Wait, wait!
别走
Halt!
妈的
Fuck!
在讲故事这个行当里
In the storytelling business,
这个傻蛋吞了那颗钻石的行为
this dummy swallowing that diamond
叫做添乱子
is called a complication.
我现在不需要乱子
A complication I didn't exactly need right now.
和谈
Parley?
我们把钻石弄丢了
We lost the diamond.
什么
What?
真对不起  赛先生  有个小鬼...
We're really sorry, Mr. S. This kid...
我们根本都没拿到钻石
We never even got our hands on it.
救命
Help!
出去  滚出去
Get out! Get out of here!
你也滚
You, too! Go!
带上你那臭哄哄的熏香  滚蛋
With your fucking sage stinking my place up. Fuck off!
就是她
Here she is.
这是个小鬼
She's a child!
-赛恩尼斯先生  -她只是个孩子
- Mr. Sionis. - She's just a kid.
她...干什么
She's... What?
我们照吩咐  把哈莉·奎茵带到了楼下
We have Harley Quinn downstairs, as requested.
滚  滚开
Fuck off! Get out.
给我滚
Fucking out!
妈的  那是我的东西
Fuck! These are my things.
-这颗钻石是我的  -没错
- This diamond is my things. - Yes.
我的东西
My things!
操他妈的  我的要求不过分吧
Fucking fuck! I don't ask for much, do I?
-是的  -为什么这种事发生在我身上
- No. - Why is this happening to me?
为什么
Why?
我会帮你拿回钻石的
I'm gonna get your diamond back.
我保证
I promise.
不如我们下楼干掉那个贱人哈莉吧
Why don't we go downstairs and kill that Harley bitch?
出出气
Blow off a little steam.
我早就想干掉她了
Yeah, I have wanted to do that for quite some time.
好  我去换衣服
Okay. I'll go get changed.
妈的  卡珊
Shit, Cass.
不管多大的代价  我都要拿回我的钻石
I don't care what it takes, I want my diamond back.
我们在想办法
We're working on it.
我们先好好玩玩吧
Now, let's go have a little fun.
哈琳·奎泽尔
Harleen Quinzel.
你好  罗米
Hiya, Romy.
你知道你为什么在这里吗
Do you know why you're here?
说到我和罗曼·赛恩尼斯
When it comes to me and Roman Sionis,
这个问题的回答有很多可能性
there are a lot of possible answers to this question.
打断他司机的双腿
Breaking his driver's legs.
有一次我念错了"意式浓缩"
There's that time I called it an "Expresso."
是女人这个事实就能气死这个人
Having a vagina in the first place pisses this guy off.
不停打断他说话  就像我现在这样
Constantly interrupting him, like I'm doing right now.
-你来是因为...  -天呐  别说了
- You're here because... - Oh, God, stop.
你要一边打开一箱子
You're gonna do that thing where you open up
奇怪的酷刑工具
a weird-ass case of torture devices
一边让人难以理解地细说你的宏伟计划
while inexplicably detailing your master plan
还有我怎么不配合你
and how I don't fit into it.
我正在构建一个更好的...
I'm building a better...
说真的  你不必这么做  真的
Seriously, you don't have to. Really!
你在构建一个犯罪帝国
You're building a criminal empire
因为老爸把你从杰纳斯集团赶出去了
because Daddy kicked you out of Janus Corp.
你觉得这么做是向他示威
And you think this is a big "Fuck you,"
但其实是为了赢回他的尊重
but in actuality it's a very misguided attempt
这样做反而会误入歧途
to win back his respect.
我懂  你真的没你自己想的那么复杂
I get it. You're really not as complicated as you think.
你也没你自己想的那么聪明
And you're really not as clever as you think,
-因为我现在要割开你的喉咙  -圣诞老爷
- because now I'm gonna slice your... - Oh, Jesus Christmas.
现在你会说你要杀了我以儆效尤
Now you're gonna say that you wanna kill me to set an example.
天呐  你太没创意了
Christ, you're boring.
-我要杀了你  -妈的
- I wanna kill you... - Shit.
因为没有了小丑罩着你
...because without the Joker around,
我可以杀你
I can.
就算你叽叽喳喳说个不停
For all your noise and bluster,
但也不过就是个傻姑娘
you're just a silly little girl
没人在身边保护你
with no one around to protect her.
-等等  -怎么
- Wait. - What?
-别杀我  -想得美
- Don't kill me. - Ha! Right.
不不不  说认真的  罗米  罗曼
No, no, no. Seriously. Romy, Roman.
别这样  我们肯定可以
Come on. There's gotta be something,
可以想办法解决的
something we can figure out.
等一下  你丢了东西对吧
Wait, wait! You lost something, right?
你丢了东西  我听到你说了
You lost something. I heard you say it.
丢了颗钻石
A diamond.
没错
Yeah.
我可以帮你找回钻石
I can help you find it.
说真的  看看我的口袋
Seriously. Look in my pocket.
另一个口袋
Other pocket.
我要自己创业了
I'm starting up my own business.
看到上面写什么吗  倒数第二行
See what it says? Second from the bottom.
没人比我对东区更了若指掌
I know the East End better than anybody.
你想把这钻石找回来吗  我在行
You want this diamond back? I'm your gal.
J先生有次丢了张
Mr. J once lost a rare photograph
埃莉诺·罗斯福的罕见裸照
of a nude Eleanor Roosevelt,
我在罗宾森公园的一个鸟巢里找到了
and I found it in a bird's nest in Robinson Park.
你要是放我走
If you let me go,
就暂时的  我会帮你把钻石拿回来
just for now, I'll get you that rock back.
你还能失去什么  要是你的人先找到了
What have you got to lose? If your boys find it first,
我发誓  你到时候杀我也不迟
swear to God, you can kill me later.
跟你拉钩  心划十字  以屁起誓
Pinky swear. Cross my heart, hope to fart.
你太烦人了
You're so tiresome!
你如果要我饶你一命
If you want my mercy,
封好你脸中央那个洞  给我听好
shut that hole in the middle of your face and listen.
你要去把我的钻石拿回来
You're gonna get me my diamond.
? 手上一吻或许通用 ?
? A kiss on the hand may be quite continental ?
? 但钻石才是姑娘的挚爱 ?
? But diamonds are a girl's best friend ?
? 一吻或许隆重 ?
? A kiss may be grand ?
? 但吻也付不了那公寓的房租 ?
? But it won't pay the rental on your humble flat ?
? 付不了快餐店的饭钱 ?
? Or help you at the automat ?
? 钻石 ?
? Diamonds ?
我会等着的
I will be waiting.
? 但是钻石 ?
? But diamonds ?
? 钻石才是姑娘的挚爱 ?
? Diamonds are a girl's best ?
你要在今天午夜前送来
I'll give you till midnight.
否则我就割下你这张漂亮的小脸蛋
And then I'm gonna peel off that pretty face
腌制保存
and pickle it.
懂吗
Okay?
你们可以说我老套
Call me old-fashioned,
但我一直以为
but I always thought the guy
应该是男人给姑娘钻石
was meant to get the girl a diamond.
我不会让你失望的  罗米  我保证
I won't let you down, Romy. I promise.
就定价五十万好了
Let's make it half a mil.
有人跟她竞争  这事会有趣很多
It's more fun if she's got competition.
给哥谭市所有雇佣兵发悬赏令
Send it to every mercenary in Gotham.
你就是那个没人想听的歌手
Hey, you're that singer no one listens to.
你就是那个没人喜欢的混球
Hey, you're the asshole no one likes.
老天  谁他妈给我打电话  什么事
Jesus. Who the fuck is this? What?
出事了
We've got a situation.
有个孩子  钻石在她手上
This kid, she's got the diamond.
她叫卡珊德拉·该隐
Her name's Cassandra Cain.
见鬼了
Holy fuck.
卡珊德拉·该隐在哪
Where can I find Cassandra Cain?
好了  讲明白了
Okay. Now we're good.
七号牢房
Cell seven.
谢谢  小可爱  真讨人喜欢
Thanks, doll. You're a peach.
我认识那家伙
Hey, I know that guy.
拒绝访问  拒绝访问
Access denied. Access denied.
拒绝访问  拒绝访问  拒绝
Access denied. Access denied. Denied.
拒绝  拒绝  拒绝
Denied. Denied. Denied. Denied. Denied. Denied.
这就好了
Perfect.
站住  站住
Hold up, hold up.
-记得我吗  -她偷了我的车
- Remember me? - She stole my car!
-哈莉·奎茵  -奎茵
- Harley Quinn. - Hey, Quinn!
-有本事放我们出来  -当我不在  大伙们
- Let us out, see what happens. - Don't mind me, guys.
-你杀了我的毛丝鼠  -我是来找那个小鬼的
- You killed my chinchilla! - Here for the kid.
怎么  姑娘  托你的福老子才在这里
What's up, girl? You're the reason I'm in here!
行吧  抱歉了
Yeah, sorry about that.
-你死定了  -我要杀了你  奎茵
- You're dead! - I'm gonna kill you, Quinn!
小鬼
Hey, kid.
-你是轮滑赛那疯子  -对  是我
- You're that psycho from the roller derby. - Yeah, yeah.
你是卡珊德拉·该隐吗
Are you Cassandra Cain?
对
Yeah.
你得告诉我...
I need to know where...
稍等一下
Hold, please.
哈莉
Harley...
抓到你了  小混蛋
I got you, you little shit.
你们是什么人
Who are you guys?
快跑  快跑
Go, go, go.
小鬼要抓活的
Keep the kid alive.
帮我一把
A little help.
她就非得一直逃跑吗
Does she have to keep running?
罗曼  你个有钱的混蛋
Roman, you trustafarian fuckbag.
是你
You!
离那孩子远点
Step away from the kid.
丢了
Drop it.
手机吗
The phone?
行啊
Sure.
很好  你醒了
Oh, good. You're awake.
帮我丢一下  行吗
Toss that for me, will ya?
什么情况
What the fuck?
我刚炸了谁
Who did I just blow up?
要不然是个想杀我的人
Either someone who wants me dead,
要不然是想要取你首级
or someone looking to collect
去领五十万赏金的人
the half-million dollar reward on your head.
五十万美元
Half a million dollars?
没错
Yeah.
你觉得我长得像值五十万吗
Do I look like I'm worth half a million dollars?
-不太像  -你抓错小孩了
- Not really. - You've got the wrong kid.
快点给我解开
Now, uncuff me.
可以啊
Sure.
只要你把钻石给我
As soon as you give me the diamond.
什么钻石
What diamond?
去你妈的
Fuck you!
看着我
Look at me.
干嘛
What?
我可不知道什么钻石
I don't know nothing about no diamond.
你语调中有变化
The inflection in your voice,
你没法跟我有视线接触
the way you can't hold eye contact,
你还是个肮脏的小偷
and the fact that you're a filthy little thief,
全都表明你清楚得很
all suggest that you do.
你可以直接给我  不然我也可以
Now, you can give it to me, or I can give you
把你交给钻石的主人
to the man that diamond belongs to.
不过相信我  你肯定不会喜欢
But trust me when I say, you're not gonna like
他会对你做的事
what he's gonna do to ya.
快点  给我
Now, hand it over.
这事不可能
Yeah, not gonna happen.
-再说一遍  -我说不行
- Come again? - I said I can't.
你再说一遍
One more time.
-我没法给你  -为什么
- I can't give it to you. - Why not?
因为我吞了  行了吧
Because I ate it, okay?
很好
Yes.
我们在这里干什么
What are we even doing here?
有两种办法可以把钻石从你肚子里取出来
There are two ways that diamond's coming outta ya.
这种
This way,
或者这种
or this way.
我也觉得
That's what I thought.
再说了  我家没吃的了
Also, I'm outta groceries.
你当雇佣兵多久了
So, how long you been a mercenary?
你从哪里拿到
Hey, where did you get...
你一直忙着看我的右手
You're so busy looking at my right hand,
你想都没想过我的左手
you haven't even thought about my left.
你的左手跟我的手铐在一起
Your left hand is cuffed to mine.
我得学学这招
I'll have to learn that one.
我们能买这个吗
Can we get this?
你没打算逃跑吧
You're not gonna try to run, are you?
听好  要是我真的值五十万
Look, if there's really a half mil on my head,
我觉得我最好还是
I figure I'm better off with
跟不会把我开膛破肚的人待在一起
the person who's not gonna cut me open.
行吧  但你要是想跑  我会杀了你的
Fine. But if you try to run, I will kill you.
我才不在乎你是不是孩子
I do not care that you're a kid.
我看见了
I saw that.
不过说真的  你怎么取得现在的成就的
Seriously though, how'd you get to be here?
在高大上的商店买东西
I mean, shopping at fancy-ass stores,
赚大钱  自己当老板
you're making bank, you have your own business.
你怎么做到的  告诉我吧
How'd you do it? Come on, tell me.
女人之间的秘密
Woman to woman.
小偷小摸是不错  但是我有真正的潜力
Being a pickpocket's fine and all, but I got real potential.
我要怎么变得跟你一样
I mean, how do I be like you?
疯狂的部分不用  其他的教教我
Well, except for the crazy part. But other than that.
第一  没人跟我一样
Number one, no one is like me.
哪怕只是跟我接近
If you wanted to even come close,
都得先去上医学院
you would have to go to medical school.
成为精神科医生  在疯人院工作
Become a psychiatrist, work in an asylum.
爱上你的病人
Fall in love with your patient,
帮上述病人逃离上述疯人院
break said patient out of said asylum.
开始犯罪生涯
Begin a life of crime.
跳进一桶化学物质里跟一个疯子证明自己
Jump into a vat of chemicals to prove yourself to a madman.
被蝙蝠侠逮捕
Get arrested by the Batman.
去坐牢  脖子上套着炸弹出狱
Go back to jail, get out of jail with a bomb on your neck.
拯救世界  回去坐牢  然后越狱
Save the world, go back to jail, and break out of jail
最后跟之前提到的疯子分手
before breaking up with the aforementioned madman
自立门户
and going out on your own.
第二
Number two...
一瓶插了根黄瓜的自来水
Six bucks for tap water
竟然卖六块钱
with a fucking cucumber stick in it?
这才是疯了
That's crazy.
我才不是在这家店买东西
I'm not shopping at this store.
我是在这家店抢东西
I'm robbing this store.
把这当作你的第一堂课
Consider this your first lesson.
蠢货才付钱
Paying is for dummies.
让开
Move it!
这是医生餐厅  这是医生
This is Doc's Place. And this is Doc.
莲花
Lotus flower!
-医生  你好吗  -我很好
- Hiya, Doc. How are ya? - Good.
他是我从来没有过的中国台湾祖父
He's the Taiwanese grandpa I never had.
他知道所有事  认识所有人
He knows everything and everyone.
我跟你说  这附近发生什么事
Nothing happens around here, let me tell you,
医生都会知道的
without Doc knowing about it.
而且他碰巧是唯一一个
And he happens to be the only person
真正关心我的人
who actually cares about me.
-我关心你吗  -你可关心了
- I do? - Yes, you do.
她点变态辣的32号菜很多年了
She's been ordering #32 with extra chili for many years.
第二课
Lesson number two,
吃32号菜一定要变态辣
you always want extra chili with #32.
这样就尝不出他的烂厨艺了
So you don't have to taste his cooking.
莲花  趁没人看见  你快上楼
Lotus flower, you have to get upstairs before someone sees.
所有人都在找你  还有你
Everyone's looking for you. And you.
我们知道
We know.
我告诉你  你要是想让男孩子尊重你
I'm telling you, if you want boys to respect you,
你得让他们知道你是认真的
you have to show them that you're serious.
炸点东西  枪击个人
Blow something up. Shoot someone.
男人都会注意到暴力的
Nothing gets a guy's attention like violence.
把门关上  锁起来
Shut that door. Lock it.
手脚放干净点  懂吗
Keep your sticky paws to yourself, okay?
这个地方...
This place...
不怎么样  但也比监狱牢房好吧
Well, it ain't much, but it's better than a prison cell.
也太酷了
...is so fucking dope.
我去  浴缸里是一只鬣狗吗
Shit. Is that a hyena in a bathtub?
我以那个壮男韦恩给它取名为布鲁斯
I named him Bruce after that hunky Wayne guy.
它是我的小可爱  是吧
He's my little dumpling, aren't you?
是不是呀  我的小宝贝
Aren't you, my little baby?
是不是呀  布鲁斯  是的
Aren't you, Brucey? Yes.
我爱你
I love you.
我可从没说过  我对你们的爱是同等的
I never said that. I love you both equally.
谁  那位  她是卡珊
Who, that? It's Cass.
你真可爱
You're so pretty.
这是谁
Who's this?
是一只海狸
It's a beaver.
布鲁斯想吃点好的吗  布鲁斯想吃点好的吗
Does Brucey want a treat? Does Brucey want a treat?
这是什么
What's this?
那是艺术品  别碰
It's art. Don't touch.
他是你的前任吗
He your ex or something?
你不认识他
You don't know who that is?
小丑
The Joker.
犯罪王子小丑
The Clown Prince of Crime?
我的前任疯子搭档
My former partner in madness?
仇恨小丑  屠杀小丑
The Harlequin of Hate? The Jester of Genocide?
你从没听说过他
You've never heard of him?
听着就像个混蛋
Well, sounds like a dick.
牛奶
Milk.
我不是心软什么的  但得承认
I'm not going soft or nothing, but I gotta admit,
有个小鬼在身边还是挺好的
it was kinda nice having the kid around.
我要一份32号  微辣
Give me a #32. Mild.
好的
Yeah, sure.
你是谁
Who are you?
他们叫我...
They call me...
我错了  应该先介绍你的
My bad. I should've introduced you.
我会快速说完
I'll make it quick.
认识一下哥谭市最富有
Meet the daughter of the richest,
最有权势的黑手党老大的女儿
most powerful Mafia don in Gotham City.
海伦娜·贝尔蒂内利
Helena Bertinelli.
对  就是那个贝尔蒂内利
Yep, that Bertinelli.
有一天  她回到家发现
One day, she comes home to find
全家人都在客厅里
her whole family in the living room.
妈妈
Momma.
所有流着贝尔蒂内利家族的血的人都在
Anyone and everyone with Bertinelli blood is there.
那位  那位是斯特法诺·加兰特
And that? That's Stefano Galante.
抢夺贝尔蒂内利家族的
The guy making the play for
势力和财富的人
the Bertinelli turf and fortune.
其中一位打手发现这孩子还活着
When one of the goons finds the kid alive,
这位心软的大块头把她偷偷带走
the big softy sneaks her outta there
藏在了西西里岛
and hides her away in Sicily.
她在那里由这个人的父亲和兄弟养大
Where she is raised by his own father and brother.
后两位都是杀手
Both assassins.
她在接下来的十五年里只想着复仇
She spends the next 15 years thinking only of revenge.
她开始了训练
So, she starts training.
等她准备好时
When she was ready,
我说的"准备好"是指
and by "ready" I mean
成为一个杀人不眨眼的杀人机器
a badass motherfucking killing machine,
她搬回哥谭市
she moves back to Gotham.
开始完成杀戮名单
Starts working on that kill list.
杀人她没问题  但其他的呢
She has the murder stuff down, but the rest?
你知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
还在努力中
Still a work in progress.
你知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?
十字弓杀手
The Crossbow Killer.
他们叫我...
They call me...
十字弓杀手
The Crossbow Killer.
他们叫我...
They call me...
十字弓杀手
The Crossbow Killer?
他们叫我...
They call me...
女猎人
Huntress.
她自称女猎人
She calls herself Huntress.
要我说的话  真是太酷了
Fucking fabulous, if you ask me.
你找谁呢
And who are you looking for?
这夜店不错
Great club.
奎茵抓到那个女孩了
Quinn got the girl.
然后呢
And?
然后她俩一起消失了
And they disappeared.
操
Fuck!
她在笑什么
What is she laughing at?
她在嘲笑我吗
Is she laughing at me?
是的
She is.
不  她没有  她...
No, she's not. She's...
你在笑什么  艾丽卡
What are you laughing at, Erika?
罗曼  我说给你听
Roman, you gotta hear this.
-太好笑了  -站到桌子上
- It's hilarious. - Get on the table.
你也太疯了吧
You're being a total kook.
给我站到桌子上
Get on the fucking table.
这是我的夜店  马上站上去
This is my club. Get up now.
-好吧  -快点
- Okay. - Now.
好了  跳舞
Now, dance.
跳舞  跳啊  艾丽卡
Dance. Dance, Erika!
好吧
Okay.
这裙子也太丑了
This dress is fucking hideous.
脱掉
Take it off.
把你的裙子脱了
Take your dress off.
站起来  给她割开裙子
Get up there and fucking cut it off her.
快点啊
Do it now!
把她的裙子给我脱了
Take her fucking dress off.
直接撕下来  快点
Just rip it off her. Hurry up!
快点
Hurry up!
-快动手  -对不起  对不起
- Fucking do it. - I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
快点
Do it.
好了  真美
Yeah. Beautiful.
你不会背叛我吧
You wouldn't betray me, would you?
我只是要去找那个女孩
I was just gonna go look for the girl.
不用  不用  我想让你在这里陪我
No, no, no. I want you to stay here with me.
我想让你待在我身边
I want you to stay here with me close.
你让我安心  我的小鸟
You soothe me, little bird.
很好  你拿到了
Good. You got it.
你追踪短信了吗
Did you trace the messages?
你从犯罪现场偷证据
You stole evidence from an active crime scene,
然后寄到我的办公室
and then had it sent to my office.
芮妮  你在想什么
Renee, what were you thinking?
悬赏那个孩子的人是罗曼
Roman is the one that put a price on the kid's head.
好吧  我必须这么做
Okay? I had to.
我现在没空解释...
I can't get into it right now...
芮妮  你需要帮助
Renee, you need help.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
她说得对
She's right.
你是个好警察  蒙托亚  但你迷失了方向
You are a good cop, Montoya, but you've lost your way.
什么
What?
对不起  好吧
I'm sorry. Okay?
你让我别无选择
You gave me no choice.
-你出卖了我  -对不起
- Did you sell me out? - I'm sorry.
你被停职了
You're suspended.
把你的警徽和枪交出来
Your badge and your gun, now.
如果你看过什么警匪片的话
If you've ever watched any cop movie ever,
就会明白现在开始才是关键
you know that this is when shit gets real.
警察什么都不在乎
What's the point of the badge,
还要警徽干什么
when it means fuck all anyway?
对吧  警长
Right, Captain?
警察都是在被停职后
No cop ever gets anything done
才有所作为的
until after they've been suspended.
本来我应该担心的
Which would've had me worried,
但我还有更急迫的事
only I had more pressing concerns.
所以你永远都不应该
And that is why you should never partake
缴纳联邦所得税
in paying federal income taxes.
你会碰到指甲油的
You'll ruin your nails.
谢谢
Thank you.
继续  第37课
Anyway, lesson 37.
为什么...
Why...
你说他们找不到我们的
You said they wouldn't find us.
冷静  没人知道我们在这
Chillax. No one knows we're here.
哈琳·奎泽尔  我是哥谭警察
Harleen Quinzel, this is Gotham Police.
好吧  他们知道
Okay. So they know.
赶紧溜
Let's scram.
开门
Open the door.
要命啊  海狸  场面失控了
Holy back door, Beavy. This is getting outta hand.
布鲁斯  过来
Bruce, come here.
我听到你在里面  开门
I can hear you! Open the door.
那是什么
What is that?
地狱里见吧  哈莉
See you in hell, Harley!
到桌子下面去
Get under the table!
布鲁斯  布鲁斯
Bruce? Bruce!
过来  别
Come here! No!
布鲁斯
Bruce?
过来  布鲁斯
Come here, boy. Bruce?
布鲁斯
Bruce?
说不通啊
This doesn't make sense.
没道理  我不明白
It doesn't make sense. I don't understand.
没人知道我们在这
No one knew we were here.
没人知道我们在这  除了...
No one knew we were here, except...
医生
Doc.
我的天  医生
My God. Doc?
医生  他在哪
Doc? Where is he?
医生
Doc?
我找不到布鲁斯  我找不到它  我...
I can't find Bruce. I can't find him. I...
不
No.
对不起  莲花
I'm sorry, lotus flower.
你出卖了我
You sold me out?
太多人给我开出了太高的价
Too many people offering me too much money.
我现在都有钱再开一家新的餐馆了
I have enough now to open up a new restaurant.
一家好餐馆
A really nice one.
但是  医生
But, Doc,
是我啊
it's me.
都是生意而已
It's just business.
接来下的事并不美好
This next bit ain't very pretty.
-你说得对  -哈莉
- You're right. - Harley?
他说得对
He's right.
生意就是生意
Business is business.
小鬼在我手上
I've got the kid.
但我需要重新商讨我们的条件
But I'm gonna need to renegotiate the terms of our deal.
我把她交给你后
If I hand her over,
所有追杀我的人都要收手
I want everyone who's after me to back off.
奎茵  立刻把钻石交给我
Quinn, bring me the rock now
我就保证你的安全
and I guarantee your safety.
这城里我说了算  我会保护你的
I own this town. You'll have my protection.
好吧
Fine.
一小时后在娱乐街陷阱奇幻屋见面
Meet me at Amusement Mile. The Booby Trap. In one hour.
别评头论足了
Quit judging.
扎斯
Zsasz!
来吧  小鬼
Come on, kid.
我给你找个安全地方
Let's get you somewhere safe.
找到她们了
We got them.
小鸟
Little bird!
你今晚要替扎斯先生开车
You're gonna be driving Mr. Zsasz tonight.
去娱乐街陷阱奇幻屋
Go. Fetch. Amusement Mile. The Booby Trap.
一定要留活口吗
Do we have to bring them back?
我觉得你对付得了两个小姑娘
I think you can manage a couple of little girls.
把钻石带回来就行
Just bring me back my diamond.
怎么了
What is it?
没什么
Nothing.
靠边停车
Pull over.
什么
What?
立刻给我停车
Pull the fucking car over now.
我要上厕所
I gotta take a leak.
她背叛了你  老大  她背叛了你
She betrayed you, boss. She betrayed you.
你确定
Are you sure?
你的小鸟是个该死内鬼
Your little bird's a fucking rat.
你想让我杀了她吗
You want me to kill her?
不
No.
不  不
No. No.
我去找你
I'll come to you.
我以为我们是朋友  而你...
I thought we were friends. And you...
你也看到那么多人追杀我了
You saw what it's like for me out there.
我别无选择
I didn't have a choice.
如果你在他来之前拉出来  那就万事大吉了
And if you go before he gets here, everything will be fine.
哈莉
Harley.
对不起  小鬼  真心的
I'm sorry, kid. I am.
好快
That was fast.
她在...
She's in...
卡珊德拉·该隐在哪
Where's Cassandra Cain?
又是你
You? Again?
你喝多了
Are you drunk?
来
Come on.
好
Okay.
正中胸部
Right in the tit.
卡珊德拉·该隐在哪
Where's Cassandra Cain?
卡珊
Cass.
你毁了我的三明治
You killed my sandwich!
再见  小鸟
Bye-bye, birdie.
不公平
No fair.
那真有必要吗
Was that really necessary?
你没有我了解她
You don't know her like I do.
卡珊
Cass?
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
我带你离开这里
I'm gonna get you outta here.
她真把你捆在马桶上了
Did she really tape you to a damn toilet?
真好
This is nice.
你还清醒
You're still conscious.
你还有知觉
You can still feel?
看着我  这下你是个好姑娘了吗
Look at me. Are you a good girl, now?
"我是个好姑娘  我是个好姑娘"
"I'm a good girl. I'm a good girl."
每次我亲手
I got one
送一只小鸟离开这个世界
for all the little birds
我都文一个文身
I helped fly away from this world.
我给你留了个特别位置
I'm saving a special spot for you.
就在这里
Right here.
你得安静点
You're gonna have to be quiet.
你们在做什么
What are you guys doing?
我知道钻石在哪里了
I know where the diamond is.
还在你体内吗
Is that rock still inside you?
老天
Oh, God.
停下
Stop.
搞什么  扎斯
The hell, Zsasz?
把她开膛破肚
Cut her open.
别胡闹了
Stop fucking around.
你听见了
You heard me.
把她开膛破肚
Cut her fucking open.
不  等等  她只是个孩子
Okay. No, no. No, no, no. See, she's just a kid.
你是个肮脏的内鬼
You're a filthy fucking rat.
我是内鬼
I'm a rat?
我早知道你不可信任  罗曼的小鸟
I knew you couldn't be trusted. Roman's little bird.
你这该死的小鸟
You little fucking bird.
所以他才需要我替他留神
That's why he needs me to look out for him.
所以他才需要我照顾
That's why he needs me to take care of him.
你知道你只是太多疑了  扎斯
You know you're just being paranoid, Zsasz.
是吗
Yeah?
向我证明
Prove it to me.
把她的小肚子剖开
Rip open her little tummy.
这不可能
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
马上动手  把她开膛
Now! Rip it open!
你这渣滓
You piece of shit!
不许动
Freeze!
谁也不许动
Don't fucking move.
你他妈是谁
Who the fuck are you?
去把那小鬼带来
Go get the kid.
好
All right.
退后
Back the fuck up!
-离我远点  你们全都是  -把那玩意放下来
- Get away from me. All of you. - Put that shit down.
冲他们开枪  小鬼
Shoot them, kid.
你  把那愚蠢的罗宾汉玩意放下
You, put that stupid-ass Robin Hood piece of shit down!
-卡珊  没事的  冷静...  -别动
- Cass, it's okay. Just calm... - Don't move!
好
Okay.
我不知道这是怎么回事
I don't know what the fuck is going on.
但我知道这个人渣
But I know that this shit stick...
刚刚想把我开膛
just tried to gut me.
而你
And you.
我还以为你不一样
Thought you were different.
对不起  小鬼
I'm sorry, kid.
看来我就是个坏人
I'm just a terrible person, I guess.
我重振旗鼓了
Ooh, I'm back.
我感觉我刚刚闯入了
Okay, I feel like I've just walked in on
我完全不关心的局面
something I don't give two shits about.
那家伙死了  所以我要走了  行吗
This guy's dead, so I'm just gonna get outta your hair. Cool?
不  等等  她撒谎  她是赛恩尼斯的手下
No. Wait. She's lying. She works for Sionis.
什么  我是赛恩尼斯的手下
Excuse me? I work for Sionis?
我不会让你把那小鬼卖给他的
I'm not letting you sell the kid to him.
我不是要把那小鬼卖给他
I wasn't going to sell the kid.
我是要用那小鬼做交易
I was going to trade the kid.
对  好保住你自己  对吗
Yeah. To save your own stupid skin. Huh?
我自己也不觉得光荣
I'm not proud of what I did,
但半个城市都在追杀我
but I had half the city after me.
包括该死的十字弓杀手
Even the fucking Crossbow Killer.
我不是十字弓杀手
I'm not the Crossbow Killer!
他们叫我...
They call me...
海伦娜·贝尔蒂内利
Helena Bertinelli.
该死的
For fuck's sake.
贝尔蒂内利灭门案那个吗
As in the Bertinelli massacre?
妈呀  了不得的童年阴影
Sheesh kebab. That is childhood trauma, right there.
我杀了加兰特
I killed Galante.
我杀了他的行刑队
I killed his firing squad.
我杀了维克多·扎斯
I killed Victor Zsasz.
现在我完事了
And now I'm done.
干得好
Bravo.
你们不介意的话  我要走了
So if you don't mind, I'm gonna leave now.
我真不想告诉你残忍的真相  甜心
I hate to be the one to break it to you, sweetheart,
但你的事情还没完
but you are not done.
你觉得是谁资助了加兰特夺权行动
Who do you think funded galante's little power grab, huh?
加兰特是和塞恩尼斯合作
Galante was working with Sionis.
罗曼杀了你全家就为了找那颗钻石
Roman killed your whole family looking for that rock.
你觉得他不会杀了这小鬼
You don't think he's gonna kill this kid?
那颗钻石是我们阻止他的唯一机会
That diamond is our only chance of stopping him.
伙计们  你们得看看这个
You guys. Hey, I think you should see this.
是赛恩尼斯
It's Sionis.
我们倒大霉了
We're fucked.
他带了支军队来
He bought himself an army.
他们都是冲我来的
They're all here for me.
是不是
Aren't they?
-不是  -不是吗
- No. - They're not?
不是  他们不是冲你来的
No, they're not.
你们知道那是什么意思吗
Do you know what that means?
意思是他不仅仅为那小鬼而来
That means he's not just after the kid anymore.
他是为我们所有人而来
He's after all of us.
他当然是冲我来的  我抢了他的东西
He's sure as hell after me. I just robbed him.
你背叛了他  你杀了他的好伙计
You just betrayed him. You just killed his BFF.
而你傻到要对他立案侦查
And you're dumb enough to be building a case against him.
除非我们都想要惨死
So, unless we all wanna die very unpleasant deaths
然后让罗曼搜索这小鬼的肠子
and let Roman go finger-fishing in the kid's intestinal tract,
不然我们就得合作
we're gonna have to work together.
和你
With you?
对
Yeah.
我们得合作
We're gonna work together,
我们要从这里全身而退  行吗
and we'll get outta here in one piece, okay?
行
Okay.
好吧  可以
Yeah. Okay.
行吧
Sure.
好
Yes!
但我们需要一些厉害武器
But we are gonna need some serious hardware.
这些可以吗
Will this do?
不可以
No.
完全不可以
Not at all.
我们死定了  我们都死定了
We're dead. We're fucking dead.
那个讨厌的混球  他居然全拿走了
That slimy jizznozzle! I can't believe he took it all!
我们完了
We're fucked.
-见鬼  -来看看这些
- Fuck! - Uh, there's this.
好
Okay.
朋友们  兄弟们  哥谭市的男人们
Friends, brothers, men of Gotham.
我资助你们  我保护你们
I have funded you. I've protected you.
我给你们擦屁股  让你们免受牢狱之灾
I've scratched your backs and kept you outta jail.
现在是时候回报我了
Well, now it's time to say thank you.
给那些小婊子们点厉害
Go show those little bitches
让她们知道不能招惹罗曼·塞恩尼斯
you don't mess with Roman Sionis.
活捉那个女孩  赏金五十万
Half a mil to whoever brings me the girl alive.
其他随便杀
The rest you can kill.
牛逼
Dope.
不不不  这件不行
Oh, no, no, no. Not that one.
有纪念意义  试试这件
Sentimental value. Try this.
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
什么  把两姐妹撑起来
What? Gotta take care of the girls.
这不好玩吗  就像睡衣派对一样
Isn't this fun? It's just like a sleepover.
我们应该叫披萨  调酒
We should order pizza. Make cosmos.
-哈莉  专心点  -好
- Harley, focus. - Okay. Yeah.
不错啊  你这套弓箭
Hey, nice. What the hell is up
有什么说法吗
with this bow and arrow shtick?
这不是弓箭
It's not a fucking bow and arrow.
这是十字弓  我不是十二岁
It's a crossbow. I'm not 12.
我喜欢这姑娘  她好暴躁
I love this chick. She's got rage issues.
我才不暴躁
I don't have rage issues.
心理学上认为
You know, psychologically speaking,
复仇很少能带来我们想要的宣泄
vengeance rarely brings the catharsis we hope for.
是
Yeah.
准备好了吗  坏蛋们就在外面
Are we ready? Bad guys, just outside.
见鬼  蹲下
Shit. Get down.
从这里下去
Down here!
卡珊
Cass!
-跟我来  -快走  快走
- Follow me! - Go, go, go, go!
快
Go!
天啊
Holy shit!
怎么
What?
你太酷了
You are so cool.
走了  这边
Okay. This way.
准备好  女士们
Get ready, ladies.
别担心  你能撑过去的
Don't worry. You're gonna make it.
-知道吗  -好
- Okay? - Okay.
什么鬼  快走  快走
What the... Go! Go, go, go!
操
Fuck.
该死
Shit.
Shit!
混蛋
Motherfucker.
放开我
Let me go!
抓到你了
Gotcha.
这边
This way!
快来  没事的  过来
Come on. Come on. It's okay. Come on.
你不该看到这个
You shouldn't have to see this.
给  帮我保管这个  好吗
Here, hold on to this for me, okay?
只需要想着这个
That's all you think about.
闭上眼睛  紧紧握住  知道吗
Just close your eyes and hold it tight. Okay?
趴下  快  你会安全的
Here. Get down. Come on. You'll be safe.
金丝雀
Canary!
你还好吗
You okay?
我们得走这边
We gotta go this way!
还来
More?
她怎么还有时间换鞋
When the fuck did she have time to do a shoe change?
快走
Come on.
多谢
Thanks.
蹲下
Duck!
-要发圈吗  -要
- Hair tie? - Yeah.
操
Fuck!
我来
I got him!
回来  小鬼
Get back here, kid!
小鬼在谁那里
Who's got the kid?
蹲下
Get down!
拜托  不要了
Please, no more.
原谅我了吗
So, forgive me yet?
别碰我
Get off me.
还有谁饿了  我知道一个卖玉米卷的好地方
Anyone else hungry? I know a great taco spot.
-我快饿死了  -我喜欢玉米卷
- I'm starving. - I love tacos.
真的吗
Really?
趴下  快趴下
Down! Get down!
你没事的  你没事的
You're okay. You're okay.
呼吸  保持呼吸  让我看看
Just breathe. Just breathe. Let me check it.
放开我
Get off!
我来救你
I got you.
这下高兴穿这件了吧  又性感又防弹
Aren't you glad you wore that? Sexy and bulletproof.
哈莉  不要  放开我
Harley! No! Get off me!
哈莉
Harley!
他们抓了小鬼  该死
They got the kid. Shit!
不能让他们抓走她  我相信你
We can't let them get her. I trust you.
-一颗子弹  -救救我
- One bullet? - Please help me!
谁还有子弹吗
Has anyone got any bullets?
该死  我没了
Fuck. I'm out.
我出不去  我需要穿过去
I can't get out there. I just need to get through.
-我们必须走  必须行动  -该死
- We gotta go. We gotta move. - Shit.
各位  他们上车了
Guys, they're in the car.
他们要走了
They're getting away.
-进去  -放开我
- Get in there! - Get off!
该死  我没箭了
Shit! I'm out.
快想办法  他们包围过来了
Guys, come on. They're closing in.
金丝雀  你知道你必须做什么
Canary, you know what you have to do!
捂上耳朵  你最好把她带回来
Cover your ears! You better get her back.
我就说她有迷死人的嗓音
Told ya she had a killer voice.
需要带你一程吗
Need a ride?
打她
Get her!
给我借点力
Whip me!
什么
What?
-给我借点力  -好
- Whip me! - Okay.
小鬼
Kid!
哈莉
Harley!
开枪
Shoot her!
哈莉
Harley!
踩刹车
Hit the brakes!
不
No!
小鬼
Kid!
哈莉
Harley!
我们都喜欢戏剧性  不是吗
Well, we always did share a love of the dramatic. Didn't we?
瞧瞧我们现在
And look at us now.
你不明白吗  你想杀了我
But don't you see? You're trying to kill me.
而我是唯一能保护你的人
I'm the only one who can protect you!
你明知靠自己活不了  奎茵
You know you can't stand on your own, Quinn.
你不是那种人
You're not the type!
可我呢  你需要我
But me? You need me!
罗米宝贝  问题是
Here's the thing, Romy baby.
你的保护是基于人们害怕你
Your protection is based on the fact that people are scared of you.
就像他们害怕J先生
Just like they're scared of Mr. J.
但他们应该怕的是我
But I'm the one they should be scared of.
不是你  不是J先生
Not you, and not Mr. J.
因为我是牛炸天的哈莉·奎茵
'Cause I'm Harley fucking Quinn.
该死
Shit.
真是太尴尬了
That was super embarrassing.
确实是
Sure was.
你以为你能打败我  你真是白痴
You think you can beat me? You're a fucking moron.
对不起  小鬼
I'm sorry, kid.
抱歉我曾想把你卖了
And I'm sorry I tried to sell you.
那挺混蛋的
That was a dick move.
无论如何
For what it's worth,
你让我想成为一个不那坏的人
you made me want to be a less terrible person.
如果我们要相互道歉  我也该告诉你件事
If we're apologizing for shit, I should tell you something.
谁让你说话了
Excuse me!
我偷了你的东西
I stole something from you.
你个手脚不干净的小坏蛋
You slippery-fingered little turd.
我偷了你的戒指
I took your ring.
戒指
My ring?
牛逼
Dope.
卡珊  哈莉
Cass! Harley!
我们没事
We're okay.
-你没事吧  -没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
-他死了  -是的
- He's gone? - Mmm-hmm.
很好  去他的
Good. Fuck that guy.
没错  吃玉米卷吗
Yeah. Tacos?
不  说真的
No, but seriously.
你用弓箭帅爆了
You were very impressive with that bow.
非常帅
Very impressive.
是十字弓
It's a crossbow.
非常感谢
I appreciate that. Thank you.
晨起鸡尾酒
Morning margaritas!
谢谢  我来拿
Thank you. I got you.
-你喝酒吧  小鬼  -喝
- You drink, right, kid? - Yeah.
不许
I don't think so.
我喜欢那个名字  女猎人
And I love that fucking name, Huntress.
-真的吗  -当然
- Really? - Yeah.
非常好的名字
Great name.
我喜欢你穿着紧身裤还能踢那么高
I really like how you were able to kick so high in those tight pants.
-没错  超酷  -是的
- Yeah, that is cool. - Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
多谢你的车
Thanks for the car.
不客气
You're welcome.
小鬼  如果那玉米卷饼不能让你拉屎
Kid, if that burrito doesn't make you shit,
我真不知道还有什么能
I don't know what will.
等我一下
Give me a minute.
棒
Yes!
对头
Right.
我让她试了西梅汁  泻药
I've given her prune juice, laxatives.
那小鬼的肠胃简直是钢铸的
I mean, the kid's got a stomach made of steel.
知道吗  我欠你一声抱歉
And you know what? I owe you an apology.
我吗
Me?
我低估了你  对不起
I underestimated you. And I'm sorry.
我习惯了
I'm used to it.
哈莉  把滤网拿来
Harley! Bring the colander.
女士们  我去了
Ladies.
祝你过滤开心
Have fun with that.
现在怎么办
So, what now?
赛恩尼斯不在了  但迟早
Sionis is gone, but it's just a matter of time
会有别的混蛋企图完成他开启的恶事
before some other asshole tries to finish what he started.
没错
Right.
我们必须把城市从内到外清洗干净
We gotta clean this city from the inside out.
她总是说话像八十年代电影里的警察吗
Does she always talk like the cop in a bad '80s movie,
只有我这么觉得吗
or is that just me?
去你的  去你的
Fuck you. And fuck you.
怎么
What?
我们这次干得特别棒
I mean, we were amazing there.
没错  绝对的
Yeah! Hell yeah!
我十分认同  所以我也来一下
I agree completely. So I'll do that, as well.
谢谢
Thank you.
好的
Right.
她偷了我的车
She stole my fucking car!
什么
What?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我知道你们在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
你们在想我归根结底还是混蛋
You think I'm a dick after all that.
但你们听到那警察怎么说了  赛恩尼斯不在了
But you heard what the cop said. Sionis is gone.
那几个人  她们会没事的
And those guys? They're gonna be just fine.
蒙托亚的老大去陷阱奇幻屋把混混们逮捕了
Montoya's boss picked up the gangbangers at the Booby Trap.
而且又一次把功劳都揽到自己身上
And took all the credit while he was at it. Again.
这致命一击让她明白
It was the kick in the balls she needed to see that
她无需向那些吹牛的混蛋证明自己
she had nothing to prove to those blowhard assholes.
她当天就辞职了
She quit the same day.
我们读取了钻石上的秘密银行代码
We got the secret bank codes off the diamond.
女猎人拿回了家族的钱
And Huntress got her family money back.
她用那笔钱资助了一个打击犯罪的小队
She's using it to fund a little crime-fighting outfit.
她们自称猛禽小队
They call themselves the Birds of Prey.
我称她们为傻傻善心人
I call them dorky little do-gooders.
钻石本身值一大笔钱
The rock itself was worth a chunk of change,
所以我当掉了
so I pawned it.
我用这笔钱创办了一个在东区兴风作浪的小公司
And I invested the cash in a little startup making waves in the East End.
我还找回了布鲁斯
And I found Bruce.
它在唐人街流浪
He was wandering around Chinatown.
我想这证明了鬣狗确实有九条命
I guess it proves the theory that hyenas really do have nine lives.
没错啦  我让小鬼当了我的学徒
Yeah, yeah. I made the kid my apprentice.
随你们说我心软
Call me a softy.
你们敢吗
I dare ya.
你们这些傻瓜还在看吗
Are you dummies still sitting there?
好吧  既然你们坚持了这么久
Fine. Since you stuck it out this long,
我告诉你们一个超级大秘密
I'll tell you a super-duper secret secret.
但你们不能告诉别人
But you can't tell anyone.
你们知道蝙蝠侠...
Okay. Did you know that Batman...
哈琳·奎泽尔
啤酒
敲门声
爸爸
Daddy!
混蛋
是时候了
你现在聪明了
再来四年
现在干什么
祝贺  及格就行
阿卡姆
疯人院
我的小丑大人
爱
医生餐厅
亲爱的布丁
手工制作
卡尼塔斯玉米卷饼
炸玉米粉圆饼
顶尖化工
雅努斯公司
猛禽小队和哈莉·奎茵
四分钟前
芮妮·蒙托亚
黑面具
姓名  轮滑蠢货
冤仇    打断了她的鼻子
姓名  拉尔夫·穆雷
冤仇    把他的小兄弟
喂了鬣狗
姓名  赛恩尼斯先生的司机
冤仇 下肢受了一点点小伤
姓名乐乐
冤仇 恶意整容
哈哈哈哈哈
姓名
冤仇
未知号码
我把蛋蛋剃干净就为了这吗
一周前
? 如果没有女性的话 ?
? Without a woman or a girl ?
乔先生
? 迷失在旷野中 ?
? Lost in the wilderness ?
? 迷失在苦涩中 ?
? Lost in the bitterness ?
哈莉·奎茵
精神科医生/杀手/赏金猎人/
代人遛狗/雇佣兵
哈莉·奎茵
精神科医生/杀手/赏金猎人/
代人遛狗/雇佣兵
音似"哈莉·奎茵"
姓名  罗曼·赛恩尼斯
冤仇
把他的司机弄残废了
念错了"意式浓缩"
是女人
在他的滤水壶里尿尿
叫他罗米
把口香糖黏在他桌子底下
偷遥控器
叫他"阴道胀气理查斯"
倒卖传家之宝
剧透很多电影
抢他风头
大号没冲干净
有一次打断他说话
他讲笑话我没笑
忘记垫杯垫
打嗝背字母表
糟蹋他的卫生间
没把马桶圈掀上去
吐在他的地毯上
给电视换台
打碎窗户
吃了他的午餐
毁了他的嗑药体验
放响屁
引起骚动
在他车上涂鸦
烧了他的画
哈莉·奎茵  /N杀手/赏金猎人
/代人遛狗/雇佣兵/
失物寻回/人生导师
Diamonds Are a Girl's Best Friend
歌曲及场景源自玛丽莲·梦露主演的
1953年的电影《绅士爱美人》
我会等着的
I will be waiting.
罗米  罗曼
Romy, Roman.
悬赏五十万
"卡珊"
卡珊德拉·该隐
通缉
回旋镖队长
曾出现在《自杀小队》中
拒绝访问
洒水器故障
门锁故障
悬赏五十万
"卡珊"
卡珊德拉·该隐
姓名
某个长得像弗里达·卡罗的混蛋
墨西哥女画家
冤仇
恨我
赏金
强力泻药
《自杀小队》情节
医生餐厅
姓名  医生
冤仇   无
32号  蒙古牛肉
听说你认识这个烂城市里的各色人渣
我需要你帮我找到一个人
我好像谁都认识  除了你
女...
H...
女猎人
姓名
冤仇
全年无休
堂食外卖
未知发件人
娱乐街陷阱奇幻屋  速来
在那里碰头
西梅汁
创始人码头
哈莉·奎茵事务所
牛逼二人组
猛禽小队和哈莉·奎茵